https://www.kaplanprepandachieve.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy explains how Kaplan, Inc. (“Kaplan”) uses, shares and protects personal information that we collect , including on kaptest.com, kaplanprepandachieve.com, pmbr.com, and i-human.com, including their respective subdomains (“Site(s)”).
By visiting one of our Sites or purchasing, enrolling in or using our products, services and events ("Programs"), you agree to this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time.
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Terms and Conditions.
EU Residents The Site is primarily intended for U.S. residents. If, however, you are a resident of the EU then you have additional privacy rights. These rights are additional to those described in this Privacy Policy.
California Residents: If you are a resident of the State of California you have additional privacy rights.
Information We Collect:
Personal Data is any information about an individual from which that individual can be identified.
Your name, address, phone number and bank account number are examples of personal data. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data). We collect Personal Data from you in various ways, including when you visit the Site(s), create an account with us, purchase, enroll in and use our Programs, use our Apps, answer surveys, participate in our social media communities, such as on Facebook, and when you send us feedback.
When you log-on to our websites or to our App(s), we automatically receive information from your device, including your IP address and location. We and our service providers may use “cookies” to keep, and sometimes track, information about you, and to create a personalized web experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your device’s web browser. Cookies track where you travel on our Site and what you look at and purchase. You agree to the use of cookies in this way. Most web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie.
We and our service providers may also use so-called "pixel tags", "web beacons", "clear GIFs" or similar means (collectively, "Pixel Tags") in connection with some Site pages and HTML-formatted email messages to, among other things, compile aggregate statistics about Site usage and response rates. A pixel tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel (1x1), that is ordinarily not visible to Site visitors and may be associated with cookies on the visitors’ hard drives. Pixel Tags allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of the Site, to deliver branded services, and to target our promotional or advertising campaigns and determine their effectiveness.
If your parent, school, employer or other third party purchases Programs on your behalf, or if an agent refers you to Kaplan, such third parties may provide us with Personal Data about you, including your first name, last name and email address.
We may also collect Personal Data about you from our business partners and other Kaplan owned companies.
Use of Your Personal Data: We may use your Personal Data in the following ways:
For the purpose you provided personal data, for example to enroll you in one of our Programs or respond to a specific inquiry;
To customize and personalize your learning experience to you;
To administer, support, improve and develop our business;
To send you information about Kaplan and Manhattan Prep products or services;
To send you information about select third party's products or services that may be of interest to you;
To allow you access to the Site to post your content or communicate with others; and
And as otherwise described to you at the point of collection.
Mobile Devices, Phone Calls and SMS:
If you provide Kaplan with a telephone number, such as when you purchase, enroll in or use a Kaplan Program, you agree that Kaplan may contact you by telephone and/or text message utilizing automated technology at such telephone number(s).
You understand that this consent is not required to purchase goods or services from Kaplan.
Disclosure of Your Personal Data:
We do not share your Personal Data with third parties for their marketing purposes, though we may share your Personal Data with other Kaplan companies, including Manhattan Prep.
We may disclose your Personal Data in response to legal process, to protect our rights, as otherwise required by law, or for the prevention or detection of a crime. We may share your Personal Data with trusted third parties who are delivering services to Kaplan, including those who help deliver our Programs, help us process transactions, such as charging your credit card when you make purchases, and otherwise help us operate our business. These third parties are not authorized by us to use your Personal Data except in connection with providing services to us.
Kaplan may disclose anonymous data to third parties. We may also share your information with third parties that you have specifically designated as authorized to receive information from us.
If payment for your Program was made by a third party, Kaplan may provide that third party with access to your Personal Data and other data.
If Kaplan provides You access to a Program in your capacity as a student of a school that has contracted with Kaplan, Kaplan may share your activity, performance and other data with your school, even if you paid for the Program in whole or in part yourself.
If you purchased Kaplan’s Nursing Admissions Test for application to a specific nursing school, your name and scores will be sent to that nursing school.
If we sell our company or part of it, or our business enters into a joint venture with another business entity, we may disclose your Personal Data to our new business partners or owners who may then provide you with information about their products and services.
Your Ability to Choose:
If you do not wish to continue receiving emails from us, you may unsubscribe by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails and following directions.
If you do not wish to continue receiving SMS messages from us, text “STOP” to KAPTST (527878).
You may also direct us to stop marketing to you by emailing us at ktp.dataprivacy@kaplan.com.
Transfer of Data Outside of Your Home Country: Your Personal Data will be held in the United States. Your Personal Data may also be stored, processed and accessed in other countries where Kaplan has facilities or where you are located. You consent to the transfer of your Personal Data outside your country, including to the United States.
Security and Information Retention: We employ security measures to protect your information both online and offline from access by unauthorized persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. The Personal Data we obtain from students allows Kaplan to deliver smarter, more efficient and more effective instruction.
Third Party Websites: Some of the products and services advertised on the Site(s) are sold and delivered by third parties (“Third Party Sellers”).
The Site(s) may also provide links to third party websites. This Privacy Policy governs collection and use of Personal Data by Kaplan.
This Privacy Policy does not apply to Third Party Sellers or to third party websites and Kaplan makes no representation about their data practices or policies.
Changes to this Privacy Policy: We will update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “Effective Date” at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check our Site(s) from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.
Contact:
All comments, queries and requests relating to these Terms and Conditions are welcomed and should be addressed as follows:
By mail: Kaplan Inc. 1515 W Cypress Creek Road, Fort Lauderdale, FL
33309
By email: ktplegaldept@kaplan.com
Rev. October 2020
